articlesvally.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy | ArticlesVally

We, Articlesvally, and our corporate affiliates (articlesvally, “we” or “us“), are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We believe in transparency, and we are committed to being upfront about our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy (“Policy“) explains which information we collect from you, when you (“you” or “your”, the user of our Services) access and use our website, as well as our platforms, widgets, analytics tools, and other technical applications that we may provide either through our Sites or through third-party websites  or other products and services provided by us (which, together, are referred to as the “Services“), will be processed by us, and how we use such information and protect it. The Policy also wishes to make sure that you are aware of the options available to you when you access and use our Services.

This Policy is a part of our Terms of Use found on our website. By using the Services, you consent to our collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this policy. This includes any information you choose to provide that is deemed sensitive under applicable law. This Policy only applies to Novelty’s Services. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of any third-party websites or apps.

### YOUR CONSENT

**By accessing the website, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth in the privacy policy, which includes the collection and process of your personal information (as defined below) when you decide to provide us with such information. If you disagree to any of the terms provided henceforth, you cannot access or use the website.**

Note: by law, you are not under any obligation to provide us with Personal Information. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you are in fact providing us with Personal Information at your own free will. You hereby agree that we may collect and use Personal Information pursuant to this Privacy Policy and all, if any, applicable laws and regulations.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED

  * Non-personal Information: Un-identified and non-identifiable information belonging to Users, which may be made available to the Website, or automatically collected by use of the Website. Non-personal Information does not, however, enable us to identify the person from whom the information was collected from, and largely consists of technical and aggregated usage information which is not linked whatsoever to an identifiable individual, for instance the identity and operation system/ browser, smart-phone model, operating system model, duration on the Website, Users ‘click-stream’ activity, keyboard language, etc.
  * Personal Information: Identifiable information of the individual, specifically information which identifies an individual or may with reasonable efforts or together with accessible additional information, enable an individual’s identification, or may be of private or sensitive nature. Personal Information collected by the Website entails the following kinds of information: IP address, device identifier, personal details provided in connection with use of the Website, such as name, e-mail address, phone number, and address.

Without your approval, we do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you, which is obtained, among others, through your active acceptance to the Terms and the Privacy Policy.

### HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

  * We collect information through an individual’s (User) usage of the Website. Therefore, we are conscious of your usage of the Website and may collect and record the information related to such usage, as well as using “cookies” and other tracking technologies.
  * We collect information that you provide to us voluntarily. For example, we collect Personal information which you voluntarily make available when you use the Website or contact us.

### WHY SUCH INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

  * To provide and operate our Website and related services.
  * To display or send Users marketing and advertising material, general and personalized content and advertisement.
  * To enhance the Website and to provide Users with technical assistance and support.
  * To send a User updates, notices, notifications, announcements, and additional information that relate to the Website and related services.
  * To generate cumulative statistical data and other cumulative information and/or other conclusive information that is non-personal, in which we and/or our business partners might use to operate and improve our Website and provide related services.
  * To comply with any applicable rule or regulation and/or response or defend against legal proceedings versus us or our business partners and affiliates.

### LAWFUL GROUNDS FOR COLLECTING USER INFORMATION

We gather and process a User’s information for the purposes described in the policy, based on at least one of the following legal grounds:  

  * With your consent: The Website asks for your agreement to process your personal information for specific purposes. Users have the right to withdraw consent at any given time. For instance, we ask for your consent to provide you with personalized content and ads through the use of cookies.
  * Legitimate interests: We process your information for legitimate interests while applying appropriate safeguards to protect your privacy. Meaning that we process your information for instances such as detecting, preventing, or addressing fraud, abuse, security, usability, functionality or technical issues with our services, protecting against harm to rights, property or safety of our properties, or our users, or the public as required or permitted by law; Enforcing legal claims, which includes the investigation of probable violations of this Privacy Policy; in order to comply and/or fulfill our obligation under applicable laws, regulation, guidelines, industry standards and contractual requirements, legal process, subpoena or governmental request, as well as our Terms of Service.

### STORAGE OF USER INFORMATION

Information related to Users will be maintained, processed and stored by the Website and authorized business partners, affiliates and service providers in the United States, and if necessary, in secured cloud storage, provided by a third party service provider.

While the data protection laws in the above jurisdictions may differ than the laws of your current residence or location, it is vital that you understand that we, our affiliates and our service providers who store or process such Personal Information are completely committed to keeping the information gathered protected and secured, pursuant to this Privacy Policy and industry standards, regardless of any lesser legal requirements that may apply in the User’s jurisdiction.

You hereby accept the place of storage and the transfer of information as described above.

### THE SHARING OF USER INFORMATION

We may share a User’s Personal Information with third parties (or allow them access to it) only in the outlined manners and instances:

  * To satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request, whenever we believe in good faith that it is legally bound to share such information.
  * To enforce this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use including investigation of potential violations thereof.
  * To detect, prevent, or address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * To respond to a User’s support request.
  * To respond to claims that a User’s contact information or any other private or proprietary information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been used, posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment.
  * To protect the rights, property, or personal safety of us, our Users or the general public.
  * When we undergo any change in control, which includes a merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of our assets.
  * To collect, hold and/or manage Users’ Personal Information through authorized third party service providers, as intended hereunder, who may be located outside the State of Israel (for example, Google Analytics). Such third party service providers may receive or have access to Users’ Personal Information, depending on each of their particular roles and purposes in facilitating and enhancing our Website and related services, namely to allow cloud hosting services, serving of personalized content and advertisement, analytics of functionality and usability of our Website, and we may only use it for such purposes.
  * Pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure.

For avoidance of doubt, we may share anonymized information with any other third party, at our sole discretion.

### THE USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

We use specific monitoring and tracking technologies, which includes the ones which are offered by third party service providers. These technologies are used to maintain, provide and improve the Website on an ongoing basis, and to provide a better User experience. Take note that these technologies enable us to: (i) keep track of our Users’ preferences and authenticated sessions, (ii) secure our Website by detecting abnormal behaviors, (iii) identify technical issues and improve the overall performance of our website, (iv) create and monitor analytics, and (v) deliver a User targeted and tailored advertisements based on your browsing activities and inferred interests and to track ad performance (For more information regarding this, click here: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Please see our Cookie Policy at: http://www.articlesvally.com/cookie-policy

Learn more about your choices and how to opt-out of tracking technologies:

In order to delete or block any tracking technologies, refer to the “Help” area on your internet browser for further instructions, or you may opt out of third party tracking technologies by following the instructions provided by each third party service provider in its privacy policy or visiting www.youronlinechoices.eu. Please note that deleting any of our tracking technologies or disabling future tracking technologies may prevent you from accessing certain areas or features of our website, or may otherwise adversely affect your user experience.

### MINORS

To use our Website, Users must be over the age of sixteen (16). Therefore, we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors under the age of sixteen (16) and do not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we may verify minors under the age of sixteen (16) are not using the Website.

### INFORMATION SECURITY

We employ industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of a User’s Personal Information, reduce the risks incurred from loss of information and to prevent unauthorized use of such information. However, no measure can provide absolute information security.

### DATA RETENTION

We retain Personal Information collected for as long as needed to provide Users with our services and to comply with any applicable laws and regulations. We then either delete from our systems or anonymize it without further notice to you.

If you should choose to withdraw your consent of processing your Personal Information at any given time, we will delete your Personal Information from our systems (except to the extent such data in whole or partly to comply with any applicable rule or regulation and/or response or defend against legal proceedings versus us or our affiliates).

### UPDATING, OBTAINING A COPY OF, OR DELETING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If the law applicable to you grants you such rights, you may ask to access, correct, or delete your Personal Information which is stored in our systems. You may ask for confirmation as to whether or not we process or have processed your Personal Information.

Subject to the limitations in law, you may request that we update, correct, or delete inaccurate or outdated information. You may request that we suspend the use of Personal Information whose accuracy you contest while we verify the status of that data.

Subject the limitations in law, you may be entitled to obtain the Personal Information you directly provided us (excluding data we obtained from other sources) in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and may have the right to transmit such data to another party.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights laid out, contact us at: articlesvally@gmail.com. When handling these requests we may ask for additional information to confirm your identity and your request. Please note, upon request to delete your Personal Information, we may retain such data in whole or in part to comply with any applicable rule or regulation and/or response or defend against legal proceedings versus us or our affiliates.

To find out whether these rights apply to you and regarding other privacy related matters, you can contact your local data protection authority if you have concerns regarding your rights under local law.

### UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, so visit this page frequently. We will notify you regarding substantial changes to this Privacy Policy by changing the link to the Privacy Policy in the Website. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on our Website. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the Website after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

### GENERAL INFORMATION

This Privacy Policy, its interpretation, and any claims and disputes related hereto, shall be governed by the laws of the State of Israel, without respect to its criminal law principles. Any and all such claims and disputes shall be brought in, and you hereby consent to them being litigated in and decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Tel Aviv, Israel.

If you have any questions or comments concerning the Privacy Policy laid out, please feel free to email us at: articlesvally@gmail.com and we will reply within a reasonable timeframe.
